James Kolbe Papers, 1958-2006 (bulk 1985-2006)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
James Kolbe Papers, 1958-2006 (bulk 1985-2006)
MS 539
Kolbe, James
Papers, 1958-2006 (bulk 1985-2006). This collection contains the political papers of James Kolbe that document his career as a member of the United States House of Representatives. It is organized into 3 subgroups with the bulk of the collection found in the legislative activity files as well as in campaign files and speeches. The collection also contains correspondence, legislative materials, voting records, subject files, photographs and audio visual materials.
230 linear feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
There are no restrictions on this collection.
Biographical Note
James Kolbe was born on June 28, 1942 in Evanston, Illinois but moved to a ranch in Santa Cruz County, Arizona in 1947. He attended Patagonia Union High School and graduated from the United States Capitol Page School in 1960 after serving as a US Senate Page to Barry Goldwater. He graduated from Northwestern University with a Bachelor of Arts in Political Science in 1965 and from Stanford University with a Masters of Business Administration with a concentration in Economics in 1967. He served in the United States Navy in Vietnam from 1968-1969 and the United States Naval Reserves from 1970-1977. He married Sarah Dinham in 1977 but they divorced in 1992.
In 1976 Kolbe ran for the Arizona Senate in District 14 and served 3 terms. He was majority whip from 1979 to 1982. In 1982 he ran for the US House of Representatives in the newly created 5th congressional district (later renamed the 8th district) but lost to Democrat Jim McNulty. In 1984 he ran again and won. He would then be reelected for the next 10 terms.
Kolbe served on various committees including Small Business, Budget and Selective Committee on Aging. From 1986-2006 Kolbe served on the Committee on Appropriations including serving as the chair of the Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, Export Financing and Related Programs for six years as well as the chair of the Treasury, Post Office and Related agencies subcommittee for four years.
Kolbe was a fiscally conservative Republican and social moderate. He was pro-choice and known for his expertise on trade especially the North American Free Trade Agreement. In 1996 Kolbe became the second Republican congressman to announce he was gay.
Since 2007 Kolbe has served as a senior transatlantic fellow for the German Marshall Fund of the United States. There he advises on trade, development and US assistance to foreign countries. He also works for McLarty Associates as a senior advisor.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into 3 Subgroups
Subgroup I: Personal files, 1984-2006
Series 1: Biographical Files, 1989-2004
Series 2: Financial Disclosure Reports, 1984-2006
Subgroup II: Congressional Activities, 1980-2006
Series 1: Campaign Files, 1982-2004
Series 2: Legislative Activity Files, 1981-2006
Subseries 1: 99th Congress, 1984-1986
Subseries 2: 100th Congress, 1987-1988
Subseries 3: 101st Congress, 1987-1991
Subseries 4: 102nd Congress, 1981-1994
Subseries 5: 103rd Congress, 1986-1997
Subseries 6: 104th Congress, 1986-2000
Subseries 7: 105th Congress, 1991-2002
Subseries 8: 106th Congress, 1996-2002
Subseries 9: 107th Congress, 1989-2005
Subseries 10: 108th Congress, 1996-2005
Subseries 11: 109th Congress, 2000-2006
Series 3: Voting Records, 1985-2004
Series 4: Speeches, 1981-2006
Series 5: Office Files, 1985-2006
Subseries 1: Schedules, 1986-2006
Subseries 2: Events, 1985-2006
Subseries 3: Travel, 1985-2006
Subseries 4: Staff Files, 1985-2005
Series 6: Correspondence, 1983-2006
Subseries 1: Acknowledgements and requests, 1983-2006
Subseries 2: Form letters, 1985-2006
Subseries 3: Letters from other officials, 1985-2006
Subseries 4: Constituent mail, 1985-2006
Series 7: Press Files, 1985-2006
Series 8: Subject Files, 1980-2006
Subgroup III: Media files, 1958-2008
Series 1: Photographic materials, 1958-2008
Subseries 1: Photographs, 1958-2008
Subseries 2: Negatives, 1984-2000
Subseries 3: Slides, 1983-1994
Subseries 4: Photographic Albums, 1985-2001
Series 2: Audio Visual materials, 1981-2006
Subseries 1: Video cassettes, 1981-2006
Subseries 2: Audio cassettes, 1984-2006
Subseries 3: Reels, 1987-1990
Subseries 4: Compact discs, 1998-2002
Subseries 5: Computer disks, 1998-2002
Series 3: Memorabilia, 1984-2005
Series 4: Oversize, 1988-2006
Scope and Content Note
Papers, 1958-2006 (bulk 1985-2006). This collection contains the political papers of Republican Congressman James Kolbe that document his 22 year career as a member of the United States House of Representatives in Arizona’s 5th congressional district (1985-2003) which was later renumbered to the 8th District (2003-2007). The collection includes campaign materials, legislative files including committee records and material on trade especially the North American Free Trade Agreement, voting records, speeches, office files, correspondence, press files, subject files and photographic and audio visual materials.
Bush, George, 1924-; Clinton, Bill, 1946-; Kolbe, James Thomas, 1942-; Kolbe, Jim, 1942-; Udall, Morris K.; Davis-Monthan Air Force Base (Ariz.); United States. Congress. Senate--Committees.; Fort Huachuca (Ariz.); Legislators--United States--Archives.; North American Free Trade Agreement (1992 December 17); Political campaigns--United States.; San Carlos Indian Irrigation Project in the State of Arizona (U.S.); Social security.; Tucson Rod and Gun Club; United States Politics and government--20th century.; Sierra Vista (Ariz.); Tucson (Ariz.) -- Politics and government.
Container List
- Subgroup 1: Personal Files, 1984-2006
  This subgroup contains biographical materials including an oral history transcript, and information on his sexuality such as news articles and fliers as well as financial disclosure reports.
  - Series 1: Biographical Files, 1989-2004
    This series contains biographical materials including biographies, personal remembrances, an oral history of his service in Vietnam and information about his sexuality including letters, articles, fliers, and editorials for and against his coming out.
    - Biographies, 1989-1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - General, 1999-2004 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Oral History, Naval Historical Foundation, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Sexual Orientation, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Series 2: Financial Disclosure Reports, 1984-2006
    This series contains financial disclosure reports.
    - 1984-1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 2000-2006 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Subgroup 2: Congressional Activities, 1980-2006
  This subgroup contains materials related to Kolbe’s congressional career including campaign files, legislative activity files including committee files, voting records, speeches, office files, correspondence, press files and subject files.
  - Series 1: Campaign Files, 1982-2004
    This series contains material related to Kolbe’s congressional campaigns including correspondence, fundraising events, press releases and voter surveys and polls. A small amount of material relate to his prospective races for governor. Material is arranged chronologically by campaign year and then alphabetically within each campaign year.
    - 1982; Campaign plan (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1982; Certificate of Nomination (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1982; Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1982; Direct mail (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 1982; Fundraising events (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1982; Memos and notes on meetings (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1982; Political action committee information kit (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 1982; Speeches (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 1982; Statements to the press (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 1984; Campaign plan- Kolbe for Congress '84 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 1984; Campaign surveys- Fifth Congressional District in Arizona, June, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 1984; Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 1984; Debates (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 1984; Direct mail (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 1984; District Research Book (1 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 1984; District Research Book (2 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 1984: Election results (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - 1984; Finance Committee (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 1984; Fundraising events (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 1984; Political Action Committee (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - 1984; Questionnaires (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - 1984; Report- The Sound Start; An Alternative Arms Control Proposal, Jim Kolbe (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - 1984; Speeches (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - 1984; Staff memos, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - 1986; Advertisements (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - 1986; Campaign Coordinating Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - 1986; Campaign plan (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - 1986; Campaign survey (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - 1986; Campaign survey (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - 1986; Correspondence, A-K, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 1986; Correspondence, L-Z (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - 1986; Correspondence- Responses to direct mail (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 1986; Debates (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - 1986; Development of campaign theme and plan (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - 1986; Direct mail (1 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - 1986; Direct mail (2 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - 1986; Finance Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - 1986; Finances, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 1986; Form letters (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - 1986; Fundraising events (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - 1986; Get Out the Vote (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - 1986; Media plan (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - 1986; National Conservation Foundation (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - 1986; National polls, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 1986; News clippings, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - 1986; Political action committee (1 of 3) (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - 1986; Political action committee (2 of 3) (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - 1986; Political action committee (3 of 3) (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - 1986; Press releases (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - 1986; Questionnaires (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - 1986; Re-election announcement (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - 1986; Research (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - 1986; Skinny Cats (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - 1986; Speeches (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - 1986; Staff memos, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - 1986; Staff reports (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - 1986; Sterring Committee (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - 1986; Voter surveys (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - 1988; Potential Race for Governor, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - 1988; Announcement (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - 1988; Campaign plan (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - 1988; Congratulatory letters, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - 1988; Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - 1988; Correspondence- Kolbe Council (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - 1988; Correspondence- Republican Party (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - 1988; Direct mail (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - 1988; Finances, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - 1988; Fundraising events, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - 1988; Get out the Vote (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - 1988; News clippings (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - 1988; Political Action Committee (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - 1988; Press releases (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - 1988; Questionnaires (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - 1988; Republican National Convention (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - 1988; Research (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - 1988; Research (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - 1988; River Bank, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - 1988; Schedules (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - 1988; Speeches (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - 1988; Staff memos, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - 1988; Telemarketing (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - 1988; Volunteer packet (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - 1988; Voter registration (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - 1988; Voter surveys (1 of 4) (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 1988; Voter surveys (2 of 4) (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - 1988; Voter surveys (3 of 4) (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - 1988; Voter surveys (4 of 4) (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - 1988; Weekly reports (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - 1990; Arizona Republican Party (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - 1990; Biographical information, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - 1990; Campaign plan (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - 1990; Campaign proposals, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - 1990; Certificate of Nomination (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - 1990; Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - 1990; Direct mail (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - 1990; Federal Elections Committee (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - 1990; Finance Committee (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - 1990; Finances, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - 1990; Form letters (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - 1990; Kolbe for Congress District-wide organization (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - 1990; Kolbe Council, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - 1990; News clippings, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - 1990; Political Action Committee (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - 1990; Press releases, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - 1990; Questionnaires (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - 1990; Republicans for Choice (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - 1990; Schedules (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - 1990; Skinny Cats (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - 1990; Speeches, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - 1990; Staff meetings (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - 1990; Staff memos (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - 1990; Voter surveys (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - 1992; Ad Hoc Data Committee (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - 1992; Advertising (1 of 4) (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - 1992; Advertising (2 of 4) (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - 1992; Advertising (3 of 4) (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - 1992; Advertising (4 of 4) (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - 1992; Arizona Republican Party (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - 1992; Bush-Quayle campaign (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - 1992; Certificates of Nomination (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - 1992; Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - 1992; Debates (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - 1992; Direct mail (1 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - 1992; Direct mail (2 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - 1992; Endorsements (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - 1992; Finances (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - 1992; Fundraising events (1 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - 1992; Fundraising events (2 of 3) (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - 1992; Fundraising events (3 of 3) (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - 1992; Issues (1 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - 1992; Issues (2 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - 1992; Newsletters (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - 1992; Opponent research (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - 1992; Opponent research- Beeler, Mike (1 of 3) (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - 1992; Opponent research- Beeler, Mike (2 of 3) (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - 1992; Opponent research- Beeler, Mike (3 of 3) (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - 1992; Opponent research- Toevs, Jim (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - 1992; Polling (1 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - 1992; Polling (2 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - 1992; Press kit (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - 1992; Press plan (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 1992; Questionnaires (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - 1992; Redistricting (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - 1992; Redistricting (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - 1992; Research (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - 1992; Schedules (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - 1992; Speeches (1 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - 1992; Speeches (2 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - 1992; Staff memos, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - 1992; Voter surveys (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - 1994; Advertising (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - 1994; Attack ads (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - 1994; Campaign fundraising plan (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - 1994; Campaign plan (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - 1994; Cochise County Republican Committee (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - 1994; Crime Bill (H.R. 5033) (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - 1994; Debates (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - 1994; Direct mail, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - 1994; Election plan (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - 1994; Endorsements (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - 1994; Events (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - 1994; Finances (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - 1994; Form letters (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - 1994; Fundraising events (1 of 2), 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - 1994; Fundraising events (2 of 2), 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - 1994; Issues, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - 1994; Kickoff event (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - 1994; Kolbe Congressional Club, 1993-1996 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - 1994; Kolbe Council (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - 1994; National Republican Congressional Committee (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - 1994; News clippings (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - 1994; Opponent research (1 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - 1994; Opponent research (2 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - 1994; Opponent research (3 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - 1994; Political Action Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - 1994; Polling, 1992-1994 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - 1994; Press (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - 1994; Press releases (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - 1994; Questionnaires (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - 1994; Redistricting, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - 1994; Re-election announcement day (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - 1994; Research (1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - 1994; Research (2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - 1994; Schedules (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - 1994; Speeches (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - 1994; Staff meetings (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - 1994; Staff memos (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - 1994; Town Halls (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - 1994; Tracking files (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - 1994; Voter surveys (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - 1996; Advertising (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - 1996; Arizona Republican Party (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - 1996; Campaign plan (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - 1996; Correspondence (1 of 2), 1992-1996 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - 1996; Correspondence (2 of 2), 1992-1996 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - 1996; Debates (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - 1996; Direct mail (1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - 1996; Direct mail (2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - 1996; Election results, 1992-1996 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - 1996; Events (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - 1996; Finances (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - 1996; Finkelstein, Ed materials (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - 1996; Form letters (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - 1996; Fundraising events (1 of 6) (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - 1996; Fundraising events (2 of 6) (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - 1996; Fundraising events (3 of 6) (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - 1996; Fundraising events (4 of 6) (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - 1996; Fundraising events (5 of 6) (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - 1996; Fundraising events (6 of 6) (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - 1996: Fundraising events- Bob Dole (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - 1996; Issues, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - 1996; Kolbe Advisory Committee (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - 1996; Kolbe Bios (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - 1996; Kolbe Council (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - 1996; News clippings, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - 1996; Opponent research (1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - 1996; Opponent research (1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - 1996; Press releases (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - 1996; Questionnaires (1 of 3) (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - 1996; Questionnaires (2 of 3) (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - 1996; Questionnaires (3 of 3) (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - 1996; Re-election announcement (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - 1996; Research (1 of 3), 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - 1996; Research (2 of 3), 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - 1996; Research (3 of 3), 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - 1996; Sexual Orientation (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - 1996; Speeches, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - 1996; Staff memos (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - 1996; Town Halls (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - 1996; Voting record (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - 1996; Pete Wilson event, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - 1996; Women Leaders Summit, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - 1998; Advertising (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - 1998; Arizona Republican Party (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - 1998; Campaign plan (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - 1998; Campaign schedules (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - 1998; Congressional Election Analysis, Arizona Congressional District Five (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - 1998; Correspondence (1 of 3) (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - 1998; Correspondence (2 of 3) (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - 1998; Correspondence (3 of 3) (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - 1998; Debates (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - 1998; Democrats for Kolbe (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - 1998; Direct mail (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - 1998; Election plan (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - 1998; Election results, 1996-1998 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - 1998; Endorsements (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - 1998; Events (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - 1998; Finances, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - 1998; Finkelstein vs. Kolbe et al. (1 of 4) (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - 1998; Finkelstein vs. Kolbe et al. (2 of 4) (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - 1998; Finkelstein vs. Kolbe et al. (3 of 4) (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - 1998; Finkelstein vs. Kolbe et al. (4 of 4) (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - 1998; Gerald Ford Dinner (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - 1998; Fundraising events (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - 1998; Hefley Amendment (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - 1998; Issues (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - 1998; Kolbe Advisory Committee (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - 1998; National Federation of Independent Business (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - 1998; National Republican Congressional Committee (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - 1998; News clippings (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - 1998; Opponent research (1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - 1998; Opponent research (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - 1998; Petitions (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - 1998; Pima County Republican Party (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - 1998; Press releases (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - 1998; Questionnaires (1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - 1998; Questionnaires (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - 1998; Research (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - 1998; Schedules (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - 1998; Speeches (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - 1998; Staff memos (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - 1998; Statement of Candidacy (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - 1998; Sweeney, Joseph materials, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - 1998; Tucson Rod and Gun Club (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - 1998; Vote at Home (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - 1998; Voter surveys (1 of 3) (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - 1998; Voter surveys (2 of 3) (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - 1998; Voter surveys (3 of 3) (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - 2000; Advertising, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - 2000; Arizona Republican Party, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - 2000; Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - 2000; Debate requests (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - 2000; Direct mail, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - 2000; Endorsements (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - 2000; Finances, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - 2000; Finklestein vs. Kolbe et al., 1999 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - 2000; Focus groups, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - 2000; Fundraising events (1 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - 2000; Fundraising events (2 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - 2000; Issues (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - 2000; Jamestown Associates (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 2000; Senator John McCain, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - 2000; National Republican Congressional Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - 2000; News clippings (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - 2000; Opponent research- George Cunningham (1 of 6) (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - 2000; Opponent research- George Cunningham (2 of 6) (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - 2000; Opponent research- George Cunningham (3 of 6 ) (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - 2000; Opponent research- George Cunningham (4 of 6) (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - 2000; Opponent research- George Cunningham (5 of 6) (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - 2000; Opponent research- George Cunningham (6 of 6) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - 2000; Opponent research- Mary Judge Ryan (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - 2000; Press releases, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - 2000; Redistricting, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - 2000; Speeches (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - 2000; Voter surveys (1 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - 2000; Voter surveys (2 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - 2002; Advertising, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - 2002; Candidacy Announcements, 1998-2002 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - 2002; Cochise County Republican Committee (Box 16, Folder 10)